Guide to the Kuntu Repertory Theatre Records, 1973-2013 CTC.2015.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Production Records, c. 1947-2013; I.
  - Scripts and Promptbooks, c. 1947-2011; 5.
    - Not Performed
      - Ony a Woman by Melodie Lynn Clark Thompson, 2001
      - The Oracle by E. Shockley, 2005
      - Osiris by William F. Mayfield, 1987
      - Our Short Stay by Barbara and Carlton Molette, 2003
      - Outdoor Recess by Joy Jones, 1999
      - Out of Line by Leah P. Hollis, 1990
      - The Party of the Year by Chanier Brown, Sr., Undated
      - The Pawn by Javon Johnson, 1998
      - Pill Hill author not listed, Undated
      - The Plantation by Laverne Tribble, 1967
      - The Powder Room by Charmaine Page, Undated
      - Preemptive by 'Niyi Coker, 2008
      - Presidential Timber by Barbara and Carlton Molette, 2001
      - Pretty Fire by Charlayne Woodard, 1995
      - Prisoner of Passion by Barabara Anton, 2002, 2005
      - Proud to Be Black, author/arranger unknown, Undated
      - Proverbs by T.O'dell Wright, Undated
      - Puttin' Mama in the Ground by Ms. J.E. Franklin, 1991
      - Queen Bee by William Mayfield, 1980
      - Queens of the Blues, author not listed, Undated
      - Raise the Level, author not listed, Undated
      - Rappingstone by Curtiss E. Porter, 1973
      - Reservations Cancelled by John Zygmunt, Undated
      - Retrospect for Life by Dominique Francoise Morisseau, 2003, 2006
      - Return to Crosscreek by Jamal Williams, 1992, 1999
      - Revenge of a King by Herb Newsome, Undated
      - The Ride of a Lifetime by Shaunequa Brathwaite, Undated
      - The Rights of Man (Maanusher Adhikaare) by Utpal Dutt, Undated
      - Ripples by Jeff Monahan, 1998
      - Rock Road by Michael Allen Harris, 2011
      - Romancing Stereotypes by Silas Jones, Undated
      - Root Dem Out! By Sybil Berry, 1993
      - A Rose in the Snow by Alexander "Cochise" Graves, 1983
      - Rose Cottages by Bill Buzzone, 1985
      - Rumor Has It... by Nathan James, Undated
      - The Sable Skin of the Hottentot Venus by Sybil Berry, 1993
      - Salimu from "New Black Playwrights", Undated
      - Salt of the Earth by Frank Floyd Hightower, Undated
      - A Salute to Martin Luther King arranged by Vernell A. Lillie, 1975
      - Samson and Delilah of the 90s by Wiliam F. Mayfield, 1995
      - Saving, Our Miracle! by Iyawo, Undated
      - Say it Loud, I'm Black and I'm Proud arranged by Monica Hilliard, Undated
      - The Scholarship by Johnson Martin, 1983
      - A Season For Love collage by Rob Penny and Others, Undated
      - Seasons of Love arranged by Ellonda Green, Undated
      - Secret Society by Gregory K. Allen, Undated
      - The Separation of Blood by Bridgette A Wimberly, 2006, 2007
      - The Serpent and the Dove by Gregory Kahlil Kareem Allen, Undated
      - Shoes by Ted Shine, Undated
      - Sins of the Father by Okima Haris, 2000
      - The Sirens by Richard Wesley, 1973
      - Sisters by Marsha A. Jackson, Undated
      - Skip and Stephanie by Lynda Patton, 1985
      - Solomon's Way by Ms. J.E. Franklin, 1991
      - Sometimes the Rainbow isn't Enough by Marcia Jones, 2004
      - Son Without a Father by Mrs. Zulu Sofola, Undated
      - Sons by Gregory Kahil Kareem Allen, 1993, Undated
      - Soul Shadows by Javon Johnson, 1996
      - Split Second by Dennis McIntyre, Undated
      - Spunk by Zora Nale Hurston, 1989
      - St. Stephen: A passion play by Janus Adams, 1981
      - Star Junction by Wali Jamal Abdullah, 2000
      - Star Light: Star Bright I Wish I May/ I Wish I Might arranged by Dr. Vernell Lillie, 1983
      - StarTrek: Creations by Claire M. Cohen, 1997
      - Steal Away by Ramona King, 1986, 2006
      - Sugar Holiday Melodies: A Breath of Heaven by Vernell A. Lillie, 2000
      - A Sunbeam by John Henry Redwood, 1998
      - Survival Strategies by Kimmika L. H. Williams, Undated
      - Tea by Erwin H. Lerner, 1995
      - Teddy's Somalia by Sybil Berry, 1993- 2002
      - The Temple by Charlotte A. Gibson, 1994
      - The Temptations by Robert P. Johnson, 1998
      - Tent Show by E. Shockley, 1999
      - The Third Pedestrial by Austin Sills, 1998
      - A Timely Peace by Drandon Kelly, Undated
      - Together- My Way by Joee A. Hall-Hoxter, 1988, 1990
      - Tongues of Fire by John E. Brady, 2006
      - The Tree That Grew Human by Thomas Meloncon, 1995
      - The Trial of Chaplain Jensen by Loring Mandel, 1974
      - Tripping to Nowhere by Bernice Snelson Riley, Undated
      - Turnabout by Kim El, 2009
      - Two Can Play by Trevor Rhone, 1988, 1989, 1990
      - Two Stories, One Catherine, 1995
      - Two Trains Running by August Wilson, 2006
      - Uhuru (Freedom) by Millard L. Lowe, 1968
      - Underdogs by Thomas R. Wilson, 2000
      - Untitled by Jeff Stetson, 1988
      - Untitled One-Act Play by Gary Bradford, 1986
      - Untitled script, 1994
      - Untitled (possibly Hair), author not listed (possibly Rob Penny), 2001
      - Untitled work number 1 by Joe Fitzpatrick, Jim Dechter, Tom Brezny, Undated
      - Untitled scripts, Undated
      - Untitled script segments and materials, Undated
      - Urban Boy by Timothy J. Johnson, 1996
      - Valentine Forever (Liberto) by F. M. Gaertner, 1954
      - Vernell Audrey Watson Lille and Five: Images, Ideas, Reflections From and Upon Her Past, Present and Future, Undated
      - Versa: No Affiliation With One Race or Another by Rob Penny, Undated
      - Vice and Versa and Complementarity (a Play and a Coda= full length drama) by Rob Penny, 1994
      - The Wages of Sin by Lawrence K. Jones, Undated
      - Waiting for Bonnie by Greg Lanier, 1994
      - The Wake Up Call by Lawrence V. Williams, Undated
      - Watch Out Fo' the Feet by Charles Michael Moore, 1976
      - Watermelon Blues, author not listed, Undated
      - The Way and other short plays by Rob Penny, Undated
      - We Are All People by Ruth Pearl, Undated
      - Weird, a Horror Play by Rob Penny, Undated
      - When the Ancestors Call by Elizabeth Brown-Guillory, Undated
      - When Doves Cry by Jacqui Walker, Undated
      - When the Water Turns Clear by Austin Sills, 1999
      - Where You Gonna Run? by Samuel A. Foster, Undated
      - While Older Men Speak by Kathleen Collins, 1985
      - White Chocolate by Samuel L. Kelley, 2004
      - White Clouds, Black Dreams by Alex Newell, Undated
      - Who Loves the Dancer by Rob Penny, 1985
      - Wilber Force by Keith Joseph Adkins, 2005
      - Willi T: A Janitor in the Andromeda Galaxy Spawns a New Civilization by William F. Mayfield, 1979
      - Winter in America by Nathan James, Undated
      - Without a Father by Thymi E. Turner, 1992
      - The World's Longest Kiss, author not listed, 2001
      - Ya' Need Jesus by John Dorsey, 1993
      - Yanga: An African Hero in Mexico by Charles Michael Moore, 1997
      - Young Mandela by Thomas Meloncon, 1999
  - Set & Costume Designs, 1975-2013; 6.
    This subseries contains hand-drawn and copied set and costume designs. Materials include lighting schemes, paint samples, set designs, and blue prints. They are arranged chronologically by season, then by performance, when known. The majority of set designs in this collection were created by designer Ken Ellis. Oversize designs have been housed separately.
    - Construction, design, makeup, and costume forms and guides, Undated
    - Facilities, Masonic Temple and Kelly Strayhorn Theatre, Undated
    - Facilities, Posvar Hall, 2000
    - Facilities, Stephen Foster Memorial, 1996, Undated
    - Facilities, University of Pittsburgh at Bradford, 1975
    - Property and sound charts, blank, Undated
    - The River Niger, 1976 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 1)
    - Homecoming and Wine in the Wilderness, 1976
    - Little Willie Armstrong Jones, 1977 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 2)
    - Good Black Don't Crack, 1977 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 3)
    - Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, 1978
    - Freeman, 1979
    - Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, 1981
    - Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, 1981 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 5)
    - Life in a Coloured Cocoon, 1982
    - Take on a Life: or Life in a Crowded Colored Cocoon, 1982 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 4)
    - Love to All, Lorraine, 1984
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 1984
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 1984 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 6)
    - Do Lord Remember Me, 1984
    - Who Loves the Dancer, 1985
    - Who Loves the Dancer, 1985 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 5)
    - A Question Mark on Your Face, 1985
    - Royal Relations, 1985
    - Royal Relations, 1985 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 6)
    - Steal Away, 1986
    - Steal Away, 1986 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 7)
    - The Meeting, 1986
    - Reachings and Pain in My Heart, 1987 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 8)
    - Reachings and Pain in My Heart, 1987 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 9)
    - Reachings and Pain in My Heart, 1987 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 10)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 1987 (Mapcase 27-2, Oversize 11)
    - Dilemma of a Ghost, 1988
    - Dilemma of a Ghost, 1988 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 1)
    - Two Can Play, 1988
    - The Meeting, 1988 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 2)
    - Long Time Since Yesterday, 1988 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 3)
    - Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight, 1989, 1990
    - The Amen Corner, 1990
    - The Amen Corner, 1990 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 4)
    - Lady Day at the Crawford Grill, 1990
    - Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday, 1991
    - Union Station, 1991
    - Clean Drums, 1992
    - Shakin' the Mess Outta Misery, 1992
    - Shakin' the Mess Outta Misery, 1992 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 5)
    - Good Black Don't Crack, 1992
    - Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, 1993
    - Little Willie Armstrong Jones, 1994
    - Miracle Church, 1994
    - Miracle Church, 1994 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 6)
    - Roads to the Mountaintop, 1994
    - Roads of the Mountaintop, 1994 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 7)
    - Good Black Don't Crack, 1994
    - Boppin' with the Ancestors, 1995
    - Boppin' with the Ancestors, 1995 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 8)
    - Flyin' West, 1995
    - Flyin' West, 1995 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 9)
    - Killin' and Chillin' in the Hood, 1995-1996
    - Killin' and Chillin' in the Hood, 1996 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 10)
    - Traces, 1996 (Mapcase 27-3, Oversize 11)
    - The Trial of One Short-Sighted Black Woman, 1996
    - The Trial of One Short-Sighted Black Woman, 1996 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 1)
    - Over Forty, 1996
    - Over Forty, 1996 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 2)
    - Miss Dessa, 1996
    - Miss Dessa, 1996 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 3)
    - Resurrection of Lady, Lester, 1997
    - Resurrection of Lady, Lester, 1997 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 4)
    - Tambourines to Glory, 1997
    - Blues for an Alabama Sky, 1997-1998
    - Ancestors Walking, 1998
    - Ancestors Walking, 1998 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 5)
    - Lifting, 1998-1999
    - Lifting, 1999 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 6)
    - Love to All Lorraine, 1999
    - Papa's Blues, 1999
    - Sing Black Hammer, 1999, 2006
    - Sing Black Hammer, 1999 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 7)
    - Nefartari Rising, 2000
    - Nefartari Rising, 1999-2000 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 8)
    - Zora!, 2000
    - Indigo Blues, 2000 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 9)
    - Fortunes of the Moor, 2001
    - Fortunes of the Moor, 2001 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 10)
    - Mahalia Standing on Holy Ground, 2001
    - Tap Dance Kid, 2001
    - Murderer in the Hill District, 2001
    - Lift Every Voice and Sing, 2002
    - Mumia, 2002
    - Whispers Want to Holler, 2001-2002
    - Killing Me Softly / Sun Kissing in the Hill District, 2002
    - The Conjure Man Dies, 2002
    - Sherlock Holmes and the Hands of Othello, 2002
    - Hieroglyphic Graffiti, 2002
    - Ashes to Africa, 2003
    - Cryin' Shame, 2003
    - She'll Find Her Way Home, 2003
    - Buffalo Soldiers, 2004
    - Dark Cow Girls and Prairie Queens, 2003-2004
    - Deadwood Dick, 2004
    - Sophisticated Ladies, 2004
    - Bubbling Brown Sugar, 2004
    - Bubbling Brown Sugar, 2005
    - The Conjure Man Dies, 2004
    - Jelly's Last Jam, 2005
    - Seven Guitars, 2005
    - Steal Away, 2006
    - Little Willie Armstrong Jones, 2005
    - In the Midnight Hour, 2006
    - Relativity, 2006, 2007
    - Sarafina, 2006, 2007
    - Good Black Don't Crack, 2007-2008
    - Ain't Misbehavin', 2007
    - Separation of Blood, 2007
    - Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, 2008
    - Journey of the Spirits, 2008
    - Lavender Lizards and Lilac Landmines, 2008
    - Pain in my Heart and Reachings, 2009
    - Clean Drums, 2009
    - The Slave and The Dutchman, 2009
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 2010
    - A Raisin in the Sun, 2010
    - Electronic Nigger, 2010
    - Sister Son/ji, 2010
    - The House that Carol Built, 2010
    - Radio Golf, 2010
    - Harriet Tubman Loved Somebody, 2010
    - The House that Carol Built, 2011
    - The House that Carol Built, 2011 (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 11)
    - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, 2011
    - Happy Ending, and A Day of Absence, 2012
    - Good Black Don't Crack, 2013
    - Among the Best, Undated
    - Harriet Tubman Loved Somebody, Undated
    - Killing Me Sofly, Undated
    - A New Vision, A Better Tomorrow, Undated
    - Mahalia Jackson, Undated
    - Papa's Blues, Undated
    - Slow Lives on a Humdrum, Undated
    - Traces, Undated
    - Union Station, Undated (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 12)
    - Wine in the Wilderness, Undated
    - Masonic Temple, Unidentifed Production, Undated
    - Unlabeled Set Color/Paint Designs, Undated
    - Pitt Theatre, Undated
    - Plans for Kuntu Repertory Theatre Performing Arts Center, 2001
    - Plans for Kuntu Repertory Theatre Performing Arts Center, Byham Theatre, and Playback Theater, 2000, Undated (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 3)
    - Unknown Artwork, Undated
    - Unknown Production, paint samples, Undated
    - Unknown Production, Undated
    - Unknown Productions, Undated
    - Unknown Productions, designs, paint and fabric samples, Undated (Mapcase 27-4, Oversize 7)
  - Pre and Post Production Records, 1975-2013; 7.
    This subseries includes records related to performance productions, rehearsals, auditions, and audience outreach and engagement. Records include cast lists, production research, correspondence, audition forms, and others. Materials are arranged chronologically by season. Audition records and audience feedback forms are arranged at the end of the subseries.
    - Season 1974-1975, Little Willie Armstrong Jones
    - Season 1975-1976
    - Season 1975-1976, Just Rob Penny, c. 1975
    - Season 1975-1976, Little Willie Armstrong Jones
    - Season 1975-1976, The River Niger
    - Season 1976-1977
    - Season 1976-1977, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More
    - Season 1976-1977, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1976-1977, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1976-1977, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1976-1977, Homecoming, Wine in the Wilderness, A Question Mark on Her Face
    - Season 1976-1977, Homecoming, A Question Mark on Her Face, Wine in the Wilderness
    - Season 1976-1977, Little Willie Armstrong Jones
    - Season 1976-1977, Theatre of Spontaneity Performance 6th Annual Women's Cultural Festival @ Pitt
    - Season 1977-1978
    - Season 1977-1978, Series II Pre-Production Notebook
    - Season 1977-1978, A New Vision, A Better Tomorrow
    - Season 1977-1978, Slow Lives on a Humdrum
    - Season 1978-1979
    - Season 1978-1979, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More
    - Season 1978-1979, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More
    - Season 1979-1980
    - Season 1979-1980, Freeman
    - Season 1980-1981
    - Season 1980-1981, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More
    - Season 1980-1981, In the Midnight Hour
    - Season 1981-1982
    - Season 1981-1982, The Brothers
    - Season 1981-1982, A Tribute to Vernell A. Lillie
    - Season 1981-1982, Zora: The Darktown Strutter
    - Season 1981-1982, Research materials stored with Zora: The Darktown Strutter by Laurence Holder Script, c.1982
    - Season 1982-1983
    - Season 1982-1983, I am a Black Woman
    - Season 1982-1983, The Strong Breed
    - Season 1982-1983, The Strong Breed, Props & Scene Break Down
    - Season 1982-1983, The Strong Breed
    - Season 1982-1983, Take on a Life: Or Live in a Crowded Colored Cocoon
    - Season 1982-1983, What Happens to a Dream Deferred?
    - Season 1983-1984
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1983-1984, Trouble in Mind
    - Season 1984-1985
    - Season 1984-1985, Do Lord Remember Me
    - Season 1984-1985, Do Lord Remember Me, c.1985
    - Season 1984-1985, Who Loves the Dancer
    - Season 1985-1986
    - Season 1985-1986, 1985-1985
    - Season 1985-1986, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More
    - Season 1985-1986, Lift Every Voice and Sing
    - Season 1985-1986, In Splendid Error
    - Season 1985-1986, Royal Relations
    - Season 1985-1986, Steal Away
    - Season 1986-1987
    - Season 1986-1987, The Brothers
    - Season 1986-1987, Pain in my Heart and Reachings
    - Season 1986-1987, To Be Young, Gifted, and Black
    - Season 1986-1987, When the Chickens Came Home to Roost
    - Season 1986-1987, When the Chickens Came Home to Roost
    - Season 1987-1988, Dilemma of a Ghost
    - Season 1987-1988, Dilemma of a Ghost
    - Season 1987-1988, Love, A Celebration in Black: The Ebony Man and Mahogany Woman
    - Season 1987-1988, Ma Rainey's Black Bottom
    - Season 1987-1988, Paul Robeson
    - Season 1987-1988, Still I Rise
    - Season 1988-1989, Long Time Since Yesterday
    - Season 1988-1989, Long Time Since Yesterday
    - Season 1988-1989, A Love Song for Miss Lydia
    - Season 1988-1989, Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight
    - Season 1988-1989, Still I Rise
    - Season 1989-1990
    - Season 1989-1990, Cast and Crew, Undated
    - Season 1989-1990, Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday
    - Season 1989-1990, Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday
    - Season 1989-1990, Evolution of Jazz
    - Season 1989-1990, The Meeting
    - Season 1989-1990, The Meeting, lobby display (Mapcase 27-5, Oversize 4)
    - Season 1989-1990, The Meeting
    - Season 1989-1990, The Meeting
    - Season 1989-1990, The Meeting
    - Season 1989-1990, Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight
    - Season 1989-1990, Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight
    - Season 1989-1990, Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight
    - Season 1989-1990, Two Can Play
    - Season 1989-1990, Two Can Play
    - Season 1990-1991
    - Season 1990-1991, Amen Corner
    - Season 1990-1991, Amen Corner Cast & Crew
    - Season 1990-1991, Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday
    - Season 1990-1991, Lifting
    - Season 1990-1991, Reflections: Rob Penny's Forum in Flight, Undated
    - Season 1990-1991, South African Fireflies
    - Season 1991-1992
    - Season 1991-1992, Clean Drums
    - Season 1991-1992, Clean Drums
    - Season 1991-1992, Shakin' the Mess Outta Misery
    - Season 1991-1992, Shakin' the Mess Outta Misery
    - Season 1991-1992, Union Station
    - Season 1991-1992, Union Station
    - Season 1992-1993
    - Season 1992-1993, Among the Best
    - Season 1992-1993, Diane's Heart Dries Out Still More, Undated
    - Season 1992-1993, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1992-1993, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1993-1994
    - Season 1993-1994, Billie Holiday
    - Season 1993-1994, Black Pittsburghers
    - Season 1993-1994, Black Pittsburghers
    - Season 1993-1994, Evolutions of Jazz, Edinburgh
    - Season 1993-1994, Little Willie Armstrong Jones
    - Season 1993-1994, The Miracle Church
    - Season 1994-1995
    - Season 1994-1995, Artist Biographies
    - Season 1994-1995, Evolutions of Jazz, SCI-Greene
    - Season 1994-1995, Roads of the Mountaintop
    - Season 1994-1995, Underseige Stories performed by Hittite Empire
    - Season 1994-1995, Flyin' West
    - Season 1994-1995, Flyin' West
    - Season 1994-1995, Flyin' West
    - Season 1995-1996
    - Season 1995-1996, Boppin' with the Ancestors
    - Season 1995-1996, Good Black Don't Crack
    - Season 1995-1996, Flyin' West
    - Season 1995-1996, Flyin' West
    - Season 1995-1996
    - Season 1995-1996, Killin' and Chillin' in the Hood
    - Season 1995-1996, Killin' and Chillin' in the Hood
    - Season 1995-1996, The Meeting, The Ellis School
    - Season 1996-1997
    - Season 1996-1997, Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday
    - Season 1996-1997, Over Forty
    - Season 1996-1997, Traces
    - Season 1996-1997
    - Season 1996-1997, Killin' and Chillin' in the Hood
    - Season 1996-1997, Miss Dessa
    - Season 1996-1997, The Trial of One Short Sighted Black Woman Versus Mammy Louise Safreeta Mae
    - Season 1996-1997, The Trial of One Short Sighted Black Woman Versus Mammy Louise Safreeta Mae
    - Season 1997-1998
    - Season 1997-1998
    - Season 1997-1998, Ancestors Walking
    - Season 1997-1998, Blues for an Alabama Sky
    - Season 1997-1998, Blues for an Alabama Sky research, Undated
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester Musician Bios
    - Season 1997-1998, The Resurrection of Lady Lester
    - Season 1997-1998, Still I Rise, Braddock Art Festival
    - Season 1997-1998, Tambourines to Glory
    - Season 1997-1998, Tambourines to Glory
    - Season 1997-1998, Touring Company
    - Season 1998-1999
    - Season 1998-1999, Ancestors Walking
    - Season 1998-1999, Keepers of the Dream
    - Season 1998-1999, Lifting
    - Season 1998-1999, Lifting
    - Season 1998-1999, The Meeting
    - Season 1998-1999, Papa's Blues
    - Season 1998-1999, Papa's Blues Bios
    - Season 1998-1999, Sacred Ground
    - Season 1998-1999, Singing Black Hammer
    - Season 1998-1999, Touring Company
    - Season 1999-2000
    - Season 1999-2000, Blues in Jazz Waters
    - Season 1999-2000, Love to All, Lorraine
    - Season 1999-2000, Nefertari Rising
    - Season 1999-2000, Nefertari Rising Study Guide
    - Season 1999-2000, A Raisin in the Sun
    - Season 1999-2000, A Raisin in the Sun Study Guide
    - Season 1999-2000, Zora: The Darktown Strutter
    - Season 2000-2001
    - Season 2000-2001, Vo-Du Macbeth, National Spirit Project background information
    - Season 2000-2001, Crawford Grill Presents Billie Holiday
    - Season 2000-2001, Fortunes of the Moor
    - Season 2000-2001, Fortunes of the Moor Study Guide
    - Season 2000-2001, Indigo Blues
    - Season 2000-2001, Indigo Blues Study Guide
    - Season 2000-2001, Mahalia Jackson: Standing on Holy Ground
    - Season 2000-2001, Mahalia Jackson: Standing on Holy Ground Music
    - Season 2000-2001, Mahalia Jackson: Standing on Holy Ground Study Guide
    - Season 2000-2001, Sugar-Holiday Melodies: A Breath of Heaven
    - Season 2000-2001, Tap Dance Kid
    - Season 2000-2001, Tap Dance Kid Study Guide
    - Season 2001-2002
    - Season 2001-2002, Conjure Man Dies
    - Season 2001-2002, Dowry
    - Season 2001-2002, Eighth Day of the Week
    - Season 2001-2002, Eighth Day of the Week
    - Season 2001-2002, Eighth Day of the Week
    - Season 2001-2002, Eighth Day of the Week
    - Season 2001-2002, Eighth Day of the Week
    - Season 2001-2002, Killing Me Softly
    - Season 2001-2002, Lift Every Voice and Sing Geneva College
    - Season 2001-2002, Murder on the Hill District
    - Season 2001-2002, Murder on the Hill District Study Guide
    - Season 2001-2002, Sherlock Holmes & the Hands of Othello
    - Season 2001-2002, Sherlock Holmes & the Hands of Othello Study Guide